I'm going to show you my room.
The room is a little hot.
I opened the window.
But...
It's not cool.
How far do I have to open it?
Oh, the sunlight.
I organized everything in my room I needed to.
I think majority.
But I need...
Wait, give me a second.
Minji,
Do you want to color it later?
Okay.
Guys.
I need a...
Recently...
During this promotion...
I received fan letters at once.
So...
There are so many letters.
All of them...
I want to read them one by one.
But...
There are so many.
So I'll read them little by little.
And separately...
I have another little box that I put it...
I'm putting them in.
But the thing is...
The letters that we got during...
There midnight break.
And...
What is it?
The...
In the room...
The stuff...
I don't know what I read...
And what I didn't read...
Because I did organize...
Which letters I had read and had to leave...
I'm going to read them all over again just to make sure that I read every letter that
I have but guys I'm a bit of a slow reader so I don't know if I'm going to be able to
read it all.
Yeah. Oh my god. Is this how I open the letter? I see. I don't have a letter open
cut up either.
Oh my god. What is this sticker?
Did they make it themselves?
Put it down a little deeper.
There it is.
Oh my god.
I'm going to read this one.
Oh my god. The cutest thing ever.
Hi.
Well, he's steady at my door like that.
Nevermind. I'm going to eat my late lunch.
I ate the last few bites too.
How long have we been eating?
Huh? I don't know.
See you in 10 minutes.
It's been Minji.
This is a beach break.
It's
God, it's hot in here tv is melted
It's kinda hot in here.
Give me a second guys.
I'm reading a letter.
It's not a letter.
It's a letter.
You're so nice.
I'll read all of these letters.
There's a lot.
There's a lot of letters.
I can't show you now.
Please understand if it takes a while.
It won't close.
I can't read all of them.
Woori!
I don't think this is right.
I should read all of them.
Thank you.
Be careful.
And...
They've given me a good place.
Bye, thank you.
I'm going to go to the gym.
Did you enjoy my vlog?
Australia vlog.
There were so many things.
I'm going to go to the gym.
What is this?
Cute.
The pants are so pretty.
I'm going to eat.
I'm going to go to the gym.
I thought about it while watching the vlog.
Mia.
Mia didn't come out as I thought.
People are so angry.
I think people are showing their love.
I think so.
I want to tell you something.
Mia.
Really.
Unlike Millie.
I don't like attention.
Sorry.
I don't like Mia.
I don't like her that much.
I have to touch her and hug her moderately.
Or.
I don't like her.
I really don't like her.
Mia is a cat.
It's a bit of a cat personality.
Mia is a completely puppy.
What is the name of the book I read in HANI for fun?
The book I bought?
I don't know what book it is.
I don't know.
But.
In school.
There was this like.
This little reading test thing you can do.
What should I say?
Before reading a book.
I learned how to check if it's right with me.
When I was in school.
It's like the five finger rule.
And um.
You just flip it to a random page.
And you read.
And if there's like words you can't.
Like um.
I don't know if I remember it.
But if there's.
Words that you don't know.
You pull up a finger.
And if you reach five fingers.
You either read it or you don't read it.
It was one of those two.
Anyways I don't know why I told you guys that.
I didn't do that.
I opened up a page.
And I thought it was just really interesting.
I remember it being like.
Like a collection of articles from.
Back then.
Do you want? Let's have a read.
I have a little.
I'll show you guys my room.
Maybe today.
I need to think about it.
Because.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It just seems really interesting this book.
I like how it looks as well.
Alright.
Someone.
Give me your number.
First number.
First person to give me a number.
Five.
Alright.
There's no fifth.
The fifth page is index pages.
We need.
106.
Thank you.
Feels like in class.
I'm in class right now.
I'm going to read.
Okay.
I'll do the page before.
I'll read.
Oh someone.
Just read.
I'm not sure.
We like the image.
I see.
No.
ays.
No, my bad.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I haven't read this book yet.
But I think it's...
It's like a collection of history in newspapers and letters.
I think? I'm not too sure.
But I can't wait to read it because it looks interesting.
Yeah.
I'm reading a book called The First Edition.
Oh, First Edition.
What would you call this type of book though? I'm not too sure.
This book was printed in Great Britain.
I don't know.
What is it?
I don't know why it's off.
I wanted to try it.
I did it.
It was really fun.
But now...
Oh my god.
Alright, we gotta super glue that.
Just try it now.
Alright, I made really cute something.
I got super glue over here.
I made...
I made really cute somethings.
Me...
I was doing it and then Minji came into my room and she saw me and I asked her if she wanted to join so she joined me.
And then Hyein also joined.
And that's how...
We got started.
I don't know if that's gonna stick well.
I hope it does.
I need a fix.
Hyein is a bug.
I don't know how to fix it.
This is a magnet.
Ah!
Okay.
Let's figure out how it goes in first.
Oh my god.
Okay.
And then we're gonna stick it on.
Super glue is the best guys.
But don't...
glue your fingers together.
Oh my god.
It's so cute.
Watch!
Wait.
I'm gonna die.
It's gonna die because of you guys.
Minji, you're the real man CEOs.
happening.
Yeah.
I wore my You're my self
Did my kur-
It's very crispy in here.
I think that's right.
So we're just checking them.
Just checking them.
We have a guest coming over a little bit as well.
So we need to clean our dorm.
Alright, let's check them. Where's Minji?
But it's a bit...
Ah, is it this one?
No wonder. There was like extra two.
I was like, no, I remember using up all the magnets.
But they fell out.
I guess they didn't stick too well in there, did they?
The person with the long blonde hair in the vlog is my sister.
She was...
Yeah, she's very...
up to date with everything.
I was really surprised.
The long blonde hair...
Oh my gosh!
Oh guys, I thought I superglued my finger to the thing.
But I didn't. It's alright.
And I made it really cute.
Oh, maybe we should paint it now.
I don't think we have time right now.
Can we do this for an hour?
I think we can do this for an hour.
But what if it gets too dirty?
Let's go find Minji.
Minji!
Can I come?
No, you can't.
Well, no.
Oh my gosh.
Minji!
Well, actually...
Hi, Minji.
I bought this janitor hat.
Peepi.
Peepi?
Short hair.
Peepi.
Let's go into it.
Peepi, hey there.
What?
Congratulations.
Enjoy what you're going to do.
Yourition's short,оп sino pepero o po dutano ho 쵹
Don't filter this.
Qua dea?
I don't know. I feel like...
Sorry, I just put my lip balm on.
I feel like if I move around...
I dropped the lip balm on you guys.
I feel like if I move around, it just happens to...
Guys, I also prepared a lot of presents.
I'm so proud. I think I bought a good one.
I have to pack it.
Alright, let's get this arts and crafts box.
Guys, I'm...
I'm gonna go. I'm going.
Because I have to color this.
So...
I'm going.
Don't worry.
I'll show you something else.
Okay?
Color? Right, I have to color something.
Alright.
Hello, everyone.
I'm going to go now.
Bye.
I'll keep you updated.