Where's your head?
She's a headless friend!
No, I'm not headless! I have a head!
Look at here.
Aww, pink!
Pink head!
Really cute!
Stop it!
Hi!
Why did you come to Bonnie's?
I just read the comments.
I think your face is too moist.
It's okay.
I was lost today.
We did it ourselves.
Do you guys want to see comments?
Stay in the middle.
Middle!
I'm really...
I'm sorry. I'm so awkward.
I'm going through awkward situations.
Everyone, stand here one line.
One line?
Let's show our costumes.
Can we each choose?
This can be the Christmas card.
Okay.
Okay, then, wait a minute.
Let's all focus on the characters.
Three!
I got an item.
One!
Pose like this.
Like this.
Okay.
Yes!
Yay!
Merry Christmas!
I want to turn on the music.
Wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
We can turn on the music and replace it with a ballad.
Can we sing our song?
Shall we sing our song?
How are you guys?
It's Christmas Eve today.
How are you spending your day?
I did this for the fire today.
It looks cold.
I did the same.
camaraderie
Oh, but I can't see it.
I want to get a gift quickly.
Oh, yes!
You have to explain.
Oh, my God.
We decorated the tree like this.
But I think we need some explanation.
We do this every year.
We've been doing this for a few years since we were trainees.
That's right. But today, with the BUNNYs,
I really wanted to do it with you guys.
I thought we should do it live.
I'm waiting for our Manito gifts in the tree.
Can you see it?
Can you get a little closer?
I'm looking forward to it.
Anyway, everyone...
We can't STACK BEFORE 찰칵 we sing .
Our words might change.
I've never tried advised be, but...
my mom has tried it,
and it is sweet, and not too sweet.
It's amazing.
Say, Q scars.
I got a cake.
Good job.
Yay!
I'm going to do a couple dance.
This is it.
I'm going to do it.
What are you doing?
I'll do it.
How?
I'll do it like this.
I'll be the teacher at the prom.
Okay.
Watch everyone.
I'm good at this with Minzy.
Ready, go.
I've never done this before.
How?
I'll do it with Minzy.
I'm good at this with Hyelin.
Okay.
Wait.
Viewers.
Boom!
I didn't see that coming.
Why?
Sorry.
Did you see that?
Did I wear a hat?
I found the secret of Rudolph.
Rudolph was actually a human.
She was a human.
Wait.
Anyway, we have to explain about weird money, too.
I've been doing this since I was a trainee.
We were always just having fun with each other.
I've never talked about it in front of Bunny's.
But we're the first.
Ba-bam.
For the first time.
Bunny's.
The first in 2013.
We haven't heard it live yet.
We're the first to show it.
Shall we show it here?
Of course.
I hope you like it.
Wait, wait.
I think we need to explain in English.
Okay.
Go on.
What if I know this guy?
So, we have been doing Secret Santa with each other since we were trainees for a few years now.
And we kept saying to you guys,
how we were doing Secret Santa and how everyone's...
My god, it's raining behind me.
And so, we're going to...
What's 공개인용? English.
We're going to just show you.
We're going to reveal our Secret Santas with you guys.
So, look forward because I was such a pro in 보장.
Seriously, like A+.
A+, you know, 100 points.
I was the best.
We...
We... I...
I feel like we're the ones that go full out with the decorations and the 보장.
But today, I...
No, okay.
I was like...
Because I really...
Like, the wrapping paper is key for me.
Like, it has to be pretty and it has to be perfect.
But I couldn't find the wrapping paper I wanted.
So, I was wandering around like this.
I couldn't be satisfied with the wrapping paper.
Anyways.
Should we show a little more?
Okay.
Or should we just guess who it is?
Everyone, come into one frame again.
I have an idea. Can I give it to you?
We do rock, paper, scissors and the winner brings one of these.
So, we bring it and the winner takes it.
So...
No, no.
I can't answer.
Because the gift is too...
It's revealed.
We can guess the gift.
Okay.
Oh..
Jooheon?
How would you play rock, paper, scissors?
Panneur Miaen.
Go back to Panneur Miaen.
handmade
Sorry. Sorry, guys.
I'll take care of it.
I'm a bit...
She looks like a kangaroo.
Wow, she does.
Rudolph.
Anyway.
Okay.
Mic.
I have something to say.
Like this?
Turn it over.
Like this.
Guys.
Ah!
Mic, mic.
From the top.
Like this.
I can't see.
I can see.
It's ambiguous.
We have a memory like this.
In 2023,
I'll say it as Santa.
What?
What do you mean by that?
No.
There's no Santa.
So,
From now on,
Let's reveal each other's secret Santa.
Okay.
Then, the members.
Who is it?
I...
I have an idea.
What is it?
Here.
Tingle.
One person sits here.
One person sits here,
and
members,
come and
give presents.
Hold the present with their eyes.
They're going to do this.
Who is it?
Tell me first.
Then,
You can make an announcement first.
The last person will be the winner.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Whoever loses first.
OK.
Who is it?
Rock, paper, scissors.
What is it?
You shouldn't do this.
You're this bad.
Rock, paper, scissors!
No, no, no, it's a ball.
Then what's a fist?
A ball.
I have to do it too.
Rock, paper, scissors!
What is this?
Is it a real person?
When did you express this?
It's a thumbs up.
Please do it with me, Luffy.
Rock, paper, scissors!
You and I.
Please sit down.
Which Randy are you?
Are you Spencer?
It must hurt so much!
I'll take a short break.
Okay.
I have to wash my face.
You have to close your eyes.
Okay?
Then...
Behind you.
I have one more.
No, no.
Behind you.
I can see the stars.
I'm the first.
Just do it.
I have to look at the stars.
This one is just holding a stone.
No, no.
Why are you doing this?
You can't fall.
You can't do that.
You have to be careful.
What's going up?
There's a chair.
What's this?
Wait a minute.
Then you sit down and raise your hand up here.
Oh, okay.
You raise your hand first. Then you do this.
This is too dangerous.
Okay, okay.
Here we go, everyone.
Wait a minute. I'll read the comments.
Do what you want to do now.
I can do it, too.
You're a real mess.
You're pretty.
Thank you.
Hey, don't mess with the dude.
Minzy, let's get married.
I can't.
I'm sorry, but don't read the questions.
Why are you reading the questions?
I think you want to get married.
Honey, I love you.
I think I wanna marry you.
No, everyone.
If you don't have any questions, we'll start.
Let's get started.
Morani, did you close your eyes?
Who do you think is your Manito?
Please tell me.
Me?
Me.
Um...
I...
First of all,
Should I keep closing my eyes?
I should keep closing my eyes?
You have to tell me now.
It's frustrating.
I thought it was Hyerin at first.
But that was in the beginning
Because Hyerin's face was always suspicious
Suspicious?
But after a certain period of time
Hyerin started to ask me a lot of questions
And I felt like she was talking about Manito
And when she was talking about Manito
She said that wasn't me
So I changed my mind
I thought it was Hyerin
Because Hyerin was suspicious, too
But it wasn't the reason
What?
I'd choose...
Hyerin
If you've been hit, you get given a weapon
Yes
Or you get a present
If you get hit, give me a hug
But you can't receive it
Give it to me
Then, let's move on.
It's better to find out the Manito.
Manito...
It doesn't matter.
It's better not to find out the Manito.
The mic is there, right?
I can't see it.
Are you smiling?
Close your eyes, quickly.
Minyoung.
Close your eyes.
I chose the last one.
It's Hyein.
I think so.
Roll up.
It's a mistake.
I can't see it.
Hyein chose...
Dani's choice was Hyein.
Whose was it?
It's purple.
It's a game.
It's a real game.
Hyein, if Dani's Manito is right,
please put the present on the desk.
Are you closing your eyes?
Yes.
If not,
you can leave.
We...
ah!
Ah!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
You got it.
Yay!
For no reason,
My Manito.
She knows it.
Try it.
How did I know?
I think I have like a sixth sense.
I was surprised.
First of all, I'm so proud of Rudolph.
Now, for the first time...
There are three of us now.
It's getting easier as we go back.
But as a person who sat here for the first time,
I'm so proud of myself.
Should we do the opening now or do it alone?
Or...
Should we do it one last time?
I have a gift that I didn't bring.
Okay.
It's important.
How big is it?
How good is it?
Then let's do it last.
I'm getting up.
Can't we just open it here?
I can't see it well right now.
You can take it off.
Yes.
I pressed it a little.
Then what should I do with my gift?
I'll write it on the camera.
Let's think about it.
No, the camera.
I didn't bring it at all.
It's all red.
Then hug me.
It's winter, so...
Just do what's in there.
Then we can gather later, right?
Wait.
Why?
But that's...
Let's proceed.
Then don't open it first.
Okay.
No, can't we open it?
No, we can't.
Or...
Or should we open it at once?
All of us?
When we're alone?
Then we just...
I'm sorry.
Where are you?
Okay.
Let's do it tomorrow, everyone.
The gift will be released two days later.
Okay.
I'm so curious.
Take it.
Let's think about it when we're done.
Okay.
It's me now.
I'll give you the one you wrote down here.
Okay.
It's me.
Mic.
Where's the mic?
It's hard.
The mic is always gone.
It's too...
Too...
Okay, we have to go back.
Okay.
Who do you think is your manito?
Back, back.
I...
Ah!
I keep hearing the sound of a tiger.
I like the sound of a tiger.
If it's not Hyerin...
If it's not Hyerin, it's like Dani.
Bunny's...
I'll go with Dani.
Okay.
What about you, Mojani?
If Minji's manito is right,
Then can I just read the comments?
The gift...
Please put it down in front of you.
Did you close your eyes?
Yes.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
You should start from the back.
Here, here.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
No.
No, I don't think so.
I'm pretty.
No, I'm pretty.
I'm crying.
I caught a cold.
Just like the ones I used to know.
I'm sorry.
But what about you?
You're not trying to see what your name is.
I don't know.
No, the again?
You're not trying to see Who's the Yu who Oh Seul-yoon.
The Mt.
It's not me.
Right.
K Shoot Sign A G emphasis said it would be so embarrassing if I let them love each other.
The
That's inappropriate, right?
Let's become crazy.
Your eyes.
Ah!
Why are you so good at this?
Wait a minute, why are you so good at this?
We've been doing this together for a long time
and we've become good at it.
Everyone is quick to know.
Who's next?
Snowman!
Because we have to eat the cake, so we have to do it quickly.
We have to do it quickly.
Rock, Scissors, Paper, Shoot!
I'm the last one.
Kang Yerin is...
No.
Let's go!
Kang Yerin is...
Please pick the person who you think is the manito of the day.
Wait a minute.
Now...
Min...
Hyein...
Me?
Minji, Hani...
It's important.
Hani?
What about Hani?
Hyein?
If you think you're the manito of the day,
please come to the front of the door with a present.
Please close your eyes.
I'm the present.
Close your eyes.
I'll cover your eyes with this.
Is your eye there?
What is it?
There's a second eye.
I'm scared.
What's going on?
You did a great job.
Is it a space sound?
Oh, my God.
What is it?
Oh, that's awesome.
3D sound.
Is that why you're doing this?
No.
It's longer than I thought.
Hyein, open your eyes and check your manito.
You're so funny.
I showed you my hard work.
I'm so cute.
I'm so pretty.
I'm so serious.
All the drawings are a little bit like a present.
You're so pretty.
I'll hold this for you.
Thank you, Pah.
That's all for you.
You should have seen her painting.
Yeah, I saw it.
And when she's rapping, it's really...
She actually...
It sounded like the people at the store.
Yeah.
She's a rapping pro.
She's so good.
Next.
Pink Rudolph.
What will it be?
Let's start.
Isn't it just one person?
I'll come out too.
Oh?
Okay.
Who do you think is your manito?
Tell me the name.
It's like I'm doing interrogation.
Wait, wait, wait.
Did you do something wrong?
Pink Rudolph.
Hey!
It's fast.
Hey, Yola. What are you doing?
Who am I?
My manito is...
Kang Hyerin and Kim Minji.
Of course.
My manito is...
I'm really...
Kang Hyerin.
I think it's you.
Really?
Yes.
I don't know.
I think it's right.
Then,
Kang Hyerin,
if you're a manito,
please come out in front of Hyein with a present.
Show up.
I'm your present.
Please close your eyes.
Here we go.
Hyein, if you're ready,
Please open your eyes and check.
One, two, three.
Is it right?
How did you guess it all?
Wow.
Hyein, are you ready?
Is there any present that isn't here?
Oh, look at the Rudolphs.
They look like choccy milk.
Choccy.
Stoby choccy milk.
I think the wrapping is so pretty.
You're really good at this.
Cute.
I really love this wrapping.
Purple, yellow,
sky blue, and white.
This is Hyein's favorite color.
It's so cute.
Did you do it yourself?
Okay.
For a pretty wrapping.
Last.
Wow.
I want you to know.
Let it snow again.
Stop it.
I'm not watching.
Okay.
HANI, please point out the person
you think is your favorite.
Please point out the person you think is your favorite.
Yes, please.
To be honest,
I'm the last one.
That's why I'm the last.
Who do you think is the last one?
So I...
And...
A few days ago,
I saw something on HANI.
Oh, you got a little too obvious.
Me?
What did you do?
Really?
I got it!
Hey you!
What are you doing to your Marido?
What did I do?
It was too hard.
Pony said, I'm ready for Marido.
I wrote down the name of the brand.
But it wasn't a letter.
It was a hyphen.
I didn't do it.
Huh?
No, you didn't.
Sanita's lie.
Are there two Santas?
I did it.
See you later.
But the camera is like,
Me?
Anyway, it's out.
We can't hear you now.
We can't hear you.
But I'm going to open it.
Please open your eyes and check it.
Open your eyes.
Ta-da.
Isn't the package so cute?
It's like a Millimia.
Don't show it to the side.
I did my best.
I think you're lacking in the packaging.
No, I wasn't lacking.
This was my best.
I love the tape.
It's the tape for the bar.
It's so obvious.
I did my best.
Why? I didn't like it.
So you bought the tape a while ago.
Who bought it?
Oh.
It's all revealed.
No, I did it.
Don't look.
Santa Claus is...
Santa Claus is beating Rudolph.
Do you think it makes sense?
I don't know.
I'm just looking forward to it.
Let's see the broadcast.
Oh, my God.
Wait, I need to put the wrapper over the way.
I understood you, but I don't think it makes sense.
I see.
I'm weak, and I'm making noise cause I heard you.
I heard you were taking a walk.
I was so seems fine.
I didn't do it because I really thought you did well.
Usually.
But I put the pack in a lot too much.
We followed the direction.
You don't have to say anything.
contarou
I also sighted it.
Oh?
charge
It's so cute even now.
It's like a red wrapping paper inside.
I know how hard you worked on it.
Thank you.
Let's hurry up and eat the cake.
I like wrapping.
Honestly, I care about that.
It's not like that after wrapping.
No, I need my gloves.
Open it.
Okay.
Give my money to glass.
I'm looking forward to it.
Where did everyone go?
They went behind the snow.
Rudolph's eyes are too big.
Santa, get down.
Hey, Santa, what are you doing?
It's dangerous.
It's a weird Santa.
This is the weirdest Santa.
It's Rudolph.
It's a gift to everyone in the world.
Hand Santa.
Oh, my name was erased just now.
What?
Now, behind the Morani.
Why do I like it so much?
Behind the Morani.
Morani, Morani.
They want us to change the music.
Okay, we'll change the music.
It's so cute.
Let's change the music.
Wait, let's change the music.
I'll go with what I want.
What?
You play hip hop.
I just want you.
Dance party before Hyerin arrives.
I think I need to go wash and come back.
Okay.
Go shower and come back.
Rudolph will go wash and come back.
There will be a dance party.
Done.
Oh, I'm going to go.
Who will come?
Eui- arrange the stage
Just do what you want, say what you want
Oh, there's a mood
Emotional
They're not kidding
Go, Frieza, Frieza, go, Rudolph, go
Pop off Rudolph, let's go
Wow
Go, go, go, Frieza, Pop off Rudolph
This is the place, right?
I can't open it
Maniac
I want to open it quickly
Chaerin, you're the best
But is it okay?
It's okay
Rudolph's eyes are too big
I keep getting it
Everyone, did you make a snowman this year?
No
Did you meet Santa?
One, two, three
I made it
Get out of here
I'm Chaerin
Everyone, this is the snowman I made
Can you see it?
If you look here, it's white
I made a scarf here
Here's a button
If you touch it, it makes sense
It's done
Is it a tiger?
You know that
Can I say this?
It's really funny
You know the dancing sauna
I keep saying it
I kept repeating it
I did it like a candy
I'm going to show you later
I want to show you
I'll show you my makeup
I'll show you
I did it like a candy.
Like a Christmas candy.
Good.
It's really cute.
I'll show you.
This is like a candy.
And...
Thanks, girl.
The bottom one is pink.
Wait, behind you.
It's really pretty.
I really like this remix.
Why?
Rudolph number 3 is back.
Woo!
Okay.
Yeah.
Let's turn on the...
Do you like it on or off?
I'll look at my face.
It's a bit moody.
Which one is prettier?
I like this one.
It's pretty now, so let's turn off the lights.
Let's go.
Let's go with a light mood.
Spotlight.
Empty light.
All right, let's go.
Spotlight.
You're good.
Yeah.
How do I do this?
Like this?
Like this.
Pink Rudolph.
You can stop the stage.
Okay.
No.
Come on.
Your А Morgen D reckon is pretty.
Turn on the light on.
Don't turn off.
The light Christine.
Why are you steel relaxâ?
shoulder-button please
guiding the light
Oh!
Fine.
Take your clothes back.
You're not the only one.
Not that.
Mm.
Oh!
The cotton wool that I'm in...
Hani is here too.
You're here too.
Show us
The other ones,open the lid.
Oh!
Caloripied!
Ji до tem the vous
Open the lid.
Why do I go there?
Why don't I go with her?
Oh, gosh!
It's Papa!
That's right.
It's so cute.
I love this ribbon.
It'll take an hour to get used to it.
Oh, my.
You look like a sister.
You're so pretty.
I can tell.
You look like a sister.
Oh, my.
You have one more layer.
There's more.
I think I know what this is.
You're a sister.
Why are you acting like you don't know?
Actually, she couldn't pack it.
Why?
Pack it like this.
What?
It's a cup.
It's a cup, right?
No.
You're a sister.
What I want to say is that I heard Dan-ie's songs a lot last year.
Oh, no.
So I originally wanted to give this to you last year.
So I want to give it to you last year.
But it's all-round design.
Yeah, you remember what you said.
But it's not all-round Christmas this time.
But it's cute.
It's all-round.
So what kind of design does it have?
I got it, Dan-ie.
Oh, my.
It's all-round.
I didn't know this was on the site
You like to give gifts to your sister, right?
I'll stop here
I always give gifts
I'm really good at explaining
It's a little pot
It's a plant, plant pot
Really?
Bring it back, girl
Ta-da, a rabbit
Oh my god
So cute
Show it here
You can grow it
You can plant whatever you want
Small ones, like a fertilizer
I was going to buy a fertilizer
But I didn't have time, I'm sorry
So cute
I love you
But there are two more left
I love you more and more
So cute
Okay, quickly
Number 1
I have to set it up
It's so cute
Oh my gosh, what is it?
This was bought in Japan
I went with Hani
Oh my gosh, this is so cute
But the funny thing is
While we were giving gifts to many people
Amazing
Who did you show?
Many, many
Please show us this
This is here
There are many crabs, water and pottery in the shop
I love this
Oh
Santa
Santa, is you really there?
No
But it looks so cute
So I thought you would like it
Thank you
Suga, look at this
Her face is really no joke
This is a hole
No joke
Touch it, Santa
No, this is
It's for raising a child
Is there a hole?
Yes
I don't know how to raise it
But she did it
This one is also cute and cute
You know me so well
You're so pretty
Please show this pretty too
This is so cute
This is a real
No
No, no, no
Go
Isn't it pretty?
Oh my gosh, that's so cute
It's so pretty
Really
Is it a cat o'clock?
What's this package?
This is a completely dry
I did it
It's so pretty
Where did you get this?
Here
Oh my gosh, you're so good at rapping
So cute
What should I do with this?
You failed to buy mushroom lighting last time
Right
But I bought this last year
Oh, this wasn't a knife
I bought it to use it
But there are four colors
There's something that looks so good on you
It's a set with mine
Mine is light purple
Yours is mint
Yours is a couple
Oh, definitely
The入 말完了
Isn't this the sky color?
It's a bit shine
Jesus
Light blue, sky blue
Wow
So cute
You look so good
Like this
Mushroom passport that will go to the sky
Oh my god
It came out perfectly
It came out perfect
Win
Thank you so much.
So cute. Oh my god.
Oh my god.
And thumbs up. They're all over the place.
This one.
So cute.
I really like this kind of thing.
Right. It was just like that.
They said cute.
I bought a prettier one than I expected.
I was a little surprised.
I was touched.
Who wants to open it?
I want to open it.
Okay.
We always organize it later.
So cute.
Thank you.
Who was the last one?
Dani.
Fast.
Dani is so good at wrapping things.
So cute.
You saw it earlier.
I can't do this size.
Oh my.
I thought your face would look like that.
Your cute face.
You got the perfect dance.
I'm going to open these cute things in my room.
Is it random?
It's random.
Which one do you want to get?
Oh.
I like all of them.
I want to eat all of them.
I'm choosing one of these.
I'm going to open this.
One, two, three.
Oh my god.
It's like you.
Wow, touch this.
I want to touch this.
It's so cute.
It's like a noodle.
I think I can feel it.
If you go to my room today, you'll find it.
I like it.
What's next?
It's all packed.
I made this bread.
Because we didn't have enough tape.
We didn't have enough tape.
So I made it.
Why did I get this?
I might get it.
I got spoiled.
I got this at school.
What's this?
Rudolph's cute shoes.
What is this?
Oh, little bear candle.
It smelled really good.
I put it in my room.
It smells good.
It's so cute.
You don't have to open it now.
Minji, you don't want to open it?
No, please open it.
Because this is the point.
I have so many of these.
I put them in front of my room.
It's been unboxed.
Oh my god.
This is a candle that can really burn.
You know what I mean?
I thought it would smell sweet.
But it's not sweet.
I like it.
I did it on purpose.
You got perfect.
I don't like sweet scents.
I like sweet scents.
Sometimes, someday.
But it's weird.
I think Santa likes sweet things.
He likes cookies.
And this.
I'm so excited.
What is it?
This is a highlight.
I'll show you.
This is cute.
But it was too hard to wrap.
So I just did it like this.
It's cool.
It looks like a figure.
It's a teddy bear.
I can feel the legs.
Oh my god.
So cute.
What is this?
Like this?
So cute.
Oh my god.
I saw this and it looked like you.
And you put some accessories on it.
So cute.
I thought it would be cute.
Oh my god.
You're so cute.
I didn't even get a gift from someone.
I'll put it down safely.
No.
I'll take this off.
I also have a letter.
Look forward to it.
Shoulder?
Oh my god.
Twinsies.
I heard we can put this up.
Really?
We should put two up.
They got a friend.
One is Manzoo and one is Daniel.
Because I'm bad at it.
Finally.
I feel a little hot here.
Is it hot in here?
We're in onesies.
We got another layer of skin.
I don't know.
Why are my hands like this?
Mystery.
I can't read the instructions.
You're curious, right?
Please check box.
Mystery.
I can open it.
We need a knife.
No, that's not it.
Then, wait.
No, it's fine.
We can do it.
This is not bad.
Charisma.
Oh my god.
Stop it.
You glow girl.
This is crazy.
Oh my god.
So cute.
This is really.
You use both of them.
If you open this.
Hot pink and white.
Oh my god.
You glow girl.
Did you choose the color?
If you put it on your eyes.
Makeup.
You glow girl.
Got it.
Aww.
I'm glad you like it.
I'm going to decorate it today.
Okay.
Next person.
I'll do it.
Babam.
I think this is amazing.
This is a set.
Wow, this is really good.
You can do it in the order you want.
But I drew it a little bit.
Then.
I'll do this first.
How do I open this?
Yeah.
But it's pretty.
I'm looking forward to it.
You drew it so well.
What is it?
This is a postcard.
Oh my god.
It's not special.
So cute.
We've been traveling a lot.
I suddenly remembered changing the concert in my head.
I didn't know I'd lose that.
What is it?
Oh my god.
It's a couch.
Is it a couch?
It's so cute.
It's like a plastic bag.
It's like a macaron color.
It's so cute.
It'll look good on your room.
It's so pretty.
I bought this at Hojiga Set.
I didn't know you had so many things to do.
I should carry this around.
I put it in the plastic bag in front of me.
Thank you.
You should buy this, too.
Next.
I think my face is really red.
Really?
This is my first time wearing this.
It's very hairy.
I'll wear it like this.
Oh, my God.
I think this is so cute.
It's so cute.
I like it.
It's cute.
This man wrapped it so cute.
This is so cute.
This is so pretty.
Really.
It's a rabbit.
Go up there.
So cute.
Is that a handmade?
Yes, it's a handmade.
The one in the closet is the most popular.
This is a rabbit.
It looks like a real rabbit.
So cute.
It looks like Hyerin.
I'll put it in my room.
So cute.
You'll be surprised when you read it.
I'll put this one first.
This pink box is...
What is it?
Is it what I think?
I'm really pretty.
That time...
Where is it?
We went together.
Where is it? Tell me more.
What is it?
I'll take it to the room.
This is...
It's a pencil case.
It's so pretty.
Me and Hani went to Japan for a day and a half.
We went around together.
I went to this store.
I bought it then.
I'm so happy.
I thought it was so pretty.
This color.
But I saw something else.
Then I'll buy it.
I'm so happy.
There are so many things to use in this pouch.
That's right.
There's a small pocket in here.
What?
This is so nice.
I'm taking it here.
I want to go too.
I got it. I got it.
I'm going to use this well.
This is so pretty.
It looks like Kang Yerin.
It looks like Hyelin.
Kang Yerin.
Put all the gifts in here and put it in a pouch.
Put it here.
Now?
It's so cute.
So pretty.
This is a set.
I'll open it.
I wonder what kind of set it is.
This is a set.
I love this.
I think I know what it is.
I don't know what it is.
No?
No.
Oh my god.
But recently, we've been...
That's right.
That's why I asked you.
So I was looking at it.
That's right.
It's the same one.
But I don't think it's the same.
It's different.
It's really funny if something else comes out.
Then this one, too.
This one is a little different.
This one is really good.
You had this when you bought it, right?
Yes.
It's so cute.
It's a baby kitten.
Baby kitten.
Wow, it's so cute.
This and...
Here.
Thank you.
Oh, it's piled up.
She's getting faster.
I think there's no room for them.
Oh, these guys.
The babies can't be put on the floor.
Oh my gosh.
I think I'll have to buy the one that I want to buy.
You can't hold it.
I think I'll have to buy the one I want to buy.
Oh, my gosh.
I'll buy it.
Oh my gosh.
I think this one is good.
Oh, my gosh.
I think I'll have to buy the one that I want to buy.
I really like cats and they were so cute.
But this... What is it? I've never seen a rabbit.
Oh my god.
Sylvania Family!
Because I'm into Sylvania.
I'm curious about this one.
It's not changing.
What is it?
Oh, that cute one.
A silver drop.
It's the only story that hasn't been left.
I thought it was a rabbit.
Oh!
Sorry, a silver drop.
I'll hide it in their room.
I'll leave it here.
Let's go find it.
Finally.
A tomato.
This is just...
I've given too many cute ones.
To match the balance.
Where did you buy it?
It's not a super cute one.
I'll take a look.
Come in.
Oh, is it a clothes?
Oh my god.
Oh, it looks like a single.
Single.
Oh, sister.
Oh, this is a limited edition.
Oh, when you go.
Is it a shirt?
But, but, everyone.
The back is really pretty, too.
This is the pop-up.
You're going to pop up all over the world.
Pop-up.
It's a mini-gallon to pop up.
Pop-up?
Oh, it's so cute.
Oh, cute.
It's snowman.
I don't know if the size fits well.
No, it's okay.
You know our size, right?
Thank you.
This is a sticker.
I needed something to wear inside.
That's right.
Wow.
It's a style.
Oh, my god.
Isn't it cute?
It's so cute.
Oh, my heart.
It's so cute because she's wearing it.
I'm going from spring to the end of the year.ierto
It's for our anniversary.
It's 한 사림 4.
Oh.
Thank you so much.
Jaramdar.
Jajaranda
fique.
You know draw the hook quickly?
Because I didn't want to show this stamp in the end.
Oh, yes.
Use it like this.
okay?
It's okay.
Hey you brown broodle
Oh sorry
It hurts so much
The gift box given to her
I'm sorry I couldn't bring it
Explain
I have this and one more
That's the main
I couldn't bring the main
So this is a little
It's a little light
How cool is the main?
I'll look forward to it
I'll unbox it
It's so pretty
I'll use this box too
Oh my god
I have to show you the inside
Where do you find it?
I don't know if you can see it
Here
In Hyein's room
I think it would be nice to have this kind of feeling
I think I'll put it on the cabinet
I can't think of that
The wooden cabinet
Oh my god
Hyein's legs are long
Touch the shoes
So cute
I can't find it easily
I'll put it next to this
Oh my god
It's so pretty
It's pretty
Then
Thank you Santa
It'll look good on you
Oh my god
So cute
I just gave it to you
Hidden socks
I'm putting on my sleeping socks
It's like a rainbow
Now it's three
This is so cute too
I did this a lot when I was a trainee
Cute socks like new jeans
Thank you
It's cute
Cute
Wait who's left
We love so much we became like
Me me
Let's go
Oh oh oh
Merry Christmas
I'll hit it too
I couldn't wrap it up like this
So I'd appreciate it if you could close your eyes and open it
This is too
Too obvious
So I'll just run like this
Actually it's here too
But I think this will be okay
Just put it on top
But this is
Oh god
What's with your hat man
You need to close your eyes
Okay okay
I want to eat it
Drumroll
That's little spring tea
Oh my god
It's too heavy
It's tooSince
Oh but it's right
It's white today
So cute
Oh my so cute
It looks like you
I thought of it
Keep going
Oh my god
Why why why
Can I show it
Just a trembling eyes
I'm trembling
My brows are
Oh showers
Oh my god
Gabriel
Hero
That's right
I'm some ruffian
I thought about this for a long time
Shall I take the scissors?
Powerful.
No, you're gonna hurt your thingy.
Thingy, thingy.
Oh my god.
So cute.
We have rabbit scissors.
No, no, no.
Oh my god.
It's the best, right?
Do it then.
I really thought about it.
Do it. Do it.
Do it.
I had one thing.
A similar style.
It looks good on you.
Good job.
It's okay, it's okay.
Yeah, good job, my manita.
But I still find the bunny the funniest.
No, you don't need that.
There's a bunny.
Oh my god.
How is it, everyone?
Isn't it so cute?
So cute.
And what do we have here?
There were so many things for the bunny.
There were so many things.
I think I need to size it up a little.
All right, I'll get it.
Is it enough?
So cute.
No, it's too obvious.
Excuse, I need to get it.
Please wait guys.
Let's go to the group photo room.
Okay?
I hope they won't kill me this time.
No no, no, you didn't e KKab verlier du Rahe.
KKreem, you didn't need to be named kавлив.
If you're thinking of your own speaks,
you really don't need to be an eek,
I'll let myself go and send you some.
Please be the most.
I put it in here.
And this is the last one.
I'll have to open it.
Is it really big?
It's so cute.
I kept saying I wanted it.
I was carrying a book cover.
And Hani saw it and asked me where I bought it.
I already bought it for her birthday.
So I was like, what?
So I kept saying I didn't want it.
I was like, I just wanted it.
Thank you.
I'll have to buy a book cover.
Oh my god.
I think you'll carry it around well.
What is it?
Don't show it to them.
It's not here.
It's so cute.
Oh my god. Thank you so much.
That's it.
This is my sister's.
Oh my god.
Oh wait, we're done.
Time goes so fast.
Yeah.
It's been an hour already.
I'm going.
If I fall, it's really a secret.
Do you have a candle?
No.
Let's just imagine.
My buddies, please edit it later.
I'll do my best.
Does it blow when you do it?
Okay.
Did you guys make a wish?
Like a holiday wish.
Yeah.
3, 2, 1.
Got it.
Okay.
You wish me very hard.
Wait.
Oh, my god.
I don't have anything in my practice room.
Only tape.
What do you do?
What do you think about Manito's session?
Session?
What?
Oh, my.
What do you think of our section this time?
We did it
me
We spent a lot of time doing it.
What if you only have 3?
Stop.
What's the magic?
Yeah.
Other members prepared one, but they didn't get it yet.
Mine just arrived, but the letter is at home.
I'll give you the letter later.
And first...
Close... Each of you close your eyes.
And put your hands.
Close your eyes.
I'll be honest, you know those mouth-slippers for you?
That was kind of an early Christmas present.
Okay.
Now each reach out and pick one.
Open eyes? No, wait.
It's already opened.
Open!
Oh my god!
You picked the purple one.
I know!
That's crazy.
How did you pick that?
I picked the purple one.
Oh my god, you guys picked one.
I picked what I wanted you to pick.
That's amazing.
I think I'm really lucky this time.
I'm so lucky.
I'm so lucky that I didn't pick you.
This...
When you drink hot cocoa or coffee,
when you drink tea,
if you turn around and drink it,
It's a back-head.
I won't forgive you.
I'm gonna call it...
Pink...
Pinky...
Pinky pear.
I'm just gonna call it pear.
Oh my god.
What is this?
We're a little clumsy today.
It's like Christmas.
Okay, guys, I have not tried this,
but I've heard good things about it,
so I hope you like it.
I'm really nervous right now because I prepared this.
Then you try it first.
I can't.
Please express your taste.
Oh, really?
Eat and look forward to it.
Is this chocolate or tiramisu?
This is dark chocolate.
That's your favorite.
Okay.
I'll try to make it look good on the front.
Why are you so cute?
Love you, guys.
Love you, too.
Look at it. Look at it crumble.
I can't eat chocolate.
You should use it here.
Here.
Are you ready?
Hurry up.
That's good.
Do you want to try it first?
You don't need to say anything.
Actually,
we were with the CEO yesterday.
We had a dinner party.
Oh, right.
It's the end of the year,
so we need time to talk.
Dani is the CEO of the party.
I'm going to eat it.
It's a birthday cake.
So I bought this cake
to celebrate the birthday of the CEO.
I bought this cake to celebrate the birthday of the CEO.
But the CEO told us
to eat it.
And he said,
when we do the live show tomorrow,
you guys should eat it.
Thank you.
There's a behind story.
What's this?
It's just like cream.
It's hard.
But my mom tried it,
and it's really good.
I recommend it.
Oh, my gosh.
Blueberry.
I'm nervous.
I like cake.
I think dark chocolate cake is the best.
You like it, right?
Right?
You succeeded, right?
Honestly.
Yay! I'm so proud.
We already done for one hour.
More than one hour.
Before we wrap up,
please introduce us to our Bernie.
Great.
Let's bring the camera.
Let's get ready for the camera.
Shall we say hello and wrap up with these?
Great.
Hey, guys. Today.
I'm going to take a selfie.
It's already decided.
Okay.
Wait. What are we going to do?
Happy holidays.
Okay. Are you ready?
Three, two, one.
Happy holidays.
She's doing it herself.
We wish you a Merry Christmas.
And the tree.
Good tidings we bring.
Does everyone come in?
Okay.
Oh, my God.
It's a pretty
decorated Bernie.
It's so lovely, right?
We're going to say goodbye
to our Bernie.
Everyone.
We're going to say goodbye to our Bernie.
So, if you're going to say goodbye to Bernie,
I'll go forward like this.
Okay?
Okay.
It's so cute.
Are you ready?
Three, two, one.
Wow.